To be continued...
You'd better explain this. All of it. In detail.
All of it. In detail.
You'd better explain this. All of it.
You'd better die from the shock of it alone.
We don't have the right kind of medicine here.
Oh, please. I can't die like this.
You go. To something. He'll die if you don't. Please, you go.
Don't do it. Bye.
If I live, so does my magic. Including the part Shaoran took with my eye.
Even if he only has half, it's still too much.
He'll be completely unstoppable.
You coward! What kind of man is willing to just lay down and die like that?
No! Let him go!
I'm sorry.
Well, witch. Is there a way for us to keep this idiot from dying?
There is. However, the price might be higher than you're willing to pay.
Almost all of the underground reservoirs disappeared.
It's because of the portal that brought me here.
No. It's because of me. It was shortly after we arrived.
I found myself drawn to the mysterious power that laid deep in the water.
There's something at the bottom.
Some power that's incredibly strong.
Subaru! Subaru!
No! Stay back or it's just gonna pull you in here too!
She was sleeping. I drew her underwater through her dreams.
So you see, even if everything that happened down there was indeed inevitable, in the end it's still my fault that it happened where and when it did.
Whether it's your fault or someone else's, nothing will change the fact that the water is gone.
Perhaps I'm wrong. You look as if you may have an idea.
Yes. It's been quite a while.
It has indeed.
I have another wish to make, and now my wish is for water.
Enough to fill the cistern here.
There will be a price. Just as there was the last time we spoke when I gave you the ability to cross dimensions.
Yes, I understand.
Karogane?
Listen.
First, you must ask me to fill the underground reservoir.
It's an exchange. To repay you for taking on his wish, Subaru will give you the means to save Fi's life.
He's a vampire. His blood is the only hope Fi has now.
A vampire's body heals much more quickly than any human's does. With that blood, Fi will be able to recover.
However, preventing Fi's death is your wish. He does not wish it for himself.
Which means, reviving him will be your responsibility.
What do I need to do?
From today forward, you must be his game.
When he takes Subaru's blood, you must mix some of your own with it.
That way, yours will be the only blood he can drink, and no one innocent will be hurt.
Yuko, does that mean if anything happens to him, Fi will-
He'll die.
Very well. I understand. I accept the price. Now, give me your blood.
No, stop it.
Shut up! If you want to die so bad, I'll kill you later myself. But until then, you're going to live.
I'll do it.
But Kamui...
I won't ever let someone else drink Subaru's blood again.
Hold your arm out.
Grab him tightly. His body is changing. It will be very painful.
We should go. I don't think we need to worry about them running away.
Take the princess out of here!
What will happen to his left eye?
His eye was taken from him before ever becoming a vampire. It's too far gone now to grow back.
Also, vampires are not immortal, despite what the legends may say.
Vampires may not live forever, but they are much sturdier than humans, and they age quite a bit more slowly.
These two are purebred with considerable powers. Once his body's makeup has changed, Fi will heal as they do.
Fi's lifespan won't change much. Magicians live longer than ordinary humans, just as vampires do.
Fi's actually lived several times longer than you already.
You agreed to become his game without even understanding what it meant?
I had no choice. If we'd waited any longer to do something, he'd be dead now.
Here's the deal. I don't always understand what the witch is planning, but she's the one that Cream Puffs sought out for help.
That thing trusts her. And after all this time, I trust it.
Do you, really?
Fi!
Flux!
There's still some questions that I want answered. But first, we'll see about that reservoir.
It's the guys from the tower!
Oh, excuse me!
靴!
So there are two of you now, Kamui. Where's he from?
Sakura's feather! But how? Mokuna should have sensed it coming closer!
I took steps so that wouldn't happen.
What are you talking about?
I had to keep it safe. And this feather can protect anything in its vicinity.
Thanks to this little beauty, the tower didn't crumble even after years of acid rain.
Of course, you already know that. It was the same for City Hall, right?
Except, yours has disappeared, hasn't it?
Why do you think that, Fuma?
You have a Dreamseer among your people, one who can predict the future.
We have a Priestess as well, with similar abilities.
Even if that's true, why would you remove the feather from its place in the tower and bring it here?
You'd like to make a deal. We're offering this feather as a replacement.
And in return?
In return, you allow the people from the tower to come live here in City Hall.
We don't have much water left in our cistern. It won't hold out for long.
You have water, but you don't have a feather to protect it.
It's simple. You provide the water, we provide the feather. Both sides benefit.
There's plenty of room here for everyone to live comfortably. All we have to do is stop fighting and help each other.
What do you say?
The decision shouldn't be mine. I won't be staying here much longer.
Is that so?
You never mentioned this, Kamui. You're leaving Tokyo?
Yes.
If that's the case, we won't stand a chance of defeating the guys from the tower.
You can say that again.
Looks like we have to accept the deal.
But that belongs to Sakura! You can't keep it! It's Sakura's and it's really important!
We've been on a journey to find it for a very long time, and we lost a friend along the way. So you just can't!
Wait.
Sakura!
If this concerns the feather, please listen to me.
Open the containers now.
Whoa!
Those things look too small to hold this much water!
Right now, this water is pure. I've seen to it that it contains none of the dangerous contaminants that have affected the rest of the water on your world.
The protection is temporary. If you aren't careful, it too will become polluted.
Before this water runs out, you must find a way to heal your world.
I still don't understand how you got all that water into this little thing.
You guys have some secrets, too. And what kind of container did you have that feather in, anyway?
Whatever it is, it didn't come from this world. This place has no indigenous power. So why would there be anything here that's designed to suppress magic?
You're right. I didn't find it here at all. I brought it with me from another dimension about four years ago.
Good afternoon, Yuko. I haven't had a method of contacting you since I reached this world, but I hope you've been doing well.
You picked up that container on one of those little trips of yours, didn't you?
Yeah. That is my job, after all. I'm a hunter of sorts, and I seek things across different worlds.
Most of the time I work for clients who are searching for things of great value, but sometimes I work for myself.
I believe you two have already met my brother. He and I call ourselves hunters, though we hunt different things.
It's a pleasure to meet you. You are the vampire Subaru, right? Thank you for taking care of Seishiro, my brother.
What? You're relating to the man who's been hunting us?
As I said, my brother and I are different. Anyway, he isn't here now. Why don't you and I take care of our business before he shows up?
So, Yuko, what's the price?
Are you ready to hear it?
I am.
Whatever it is, I...
No, I'll do it!
Sakura!
If there's a price to pay, I'll pay it this time. If you wouldn't mind, please fill me in on what happened while I was sleeping.
Yuko, you can't ask that! The rain in this world burns! And there are big monsters everywhere! It's too dangerous!
It's the only way. Sakura must retrieve what I asked for without any help. That is the price.
Alright. Ready to go?
I'm so sorry. You were hurt because I asked you to stop. Rest. I hope you'll heal up soon. You get some good rest too, okay, Mokuna? I know Fi is in good hands with you here.
There's nothing I could say that would change your mind, I guess. I get it then. In that case, I'll just wish you good luck. We'll be waiting here when you get back.
Thanks.
Something wrong?
How is Seishiro?
Well, let's see. He ages more slowly, of course, and he's got more energy than I've ever seen before. He's very intent on catching up with you two. He's a hunter. He won't stop until he has.
We aren't gonna let that happen.
We'll see about that.
Come on, let's all try to keep our cool. We've got other things to worry about now.
Sha'ron.
Charon, even your name's the same as his.
Yeah.
You were locked up for a really long time.
It must have been lonely.
Not really. I saw everything.
I was watching through his eyes the whole time.
I was always there.
That must have been even harder for you.
All you could do is watch while Moken and the others had fun.
It was difficult and scary sometimes, but we still loved being together.
I'm so sorry.
You must have wanted to come along too, didn't you?
I guess I did.
Good morning, Kurokane.
Don't move.
Bye.
Yes, I'm sorry if you were worried about me.
Mokuna, I'd like you to take a little nap, but keep the transmission going.
I want to speak with Fi alone.
Have you talked to him?
I told him good morning. It wasn't a long conversation.
After everything that's happened, is that all you have to say?
You know, when we first met, I was going to call him by his full name, just like I did everyone else.
But he got so angry when I called him Kurupu that I couldn't help myself.
It was something new. I'd never called anyone by a nickname before.
It was so fun that I didn't realize I was beginning to cross the line I had drawn for myself.
But now I have a chance to fix that. I can never forgive him for saving my life.
If I did, we'd just become close again.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
Your fears are their fears. Your pain is their pain.
How's Sakura? Is she still sleeping upstairs?
No. She's gone.
Thank you.
It's not like wearing that crest is something you chose to do.
I know. But I'm sure you'd rather not look at it all the same.
The witch told me you'd been held captive all this time, by the man whose crest that is.
Yes.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
I don't know where he is or how to find him.
Even if I did know, I don't have the power to cross dimensions.
So I couldn't take you to it.
Again, I don't blame you for that.
I don't mind, wait for it.
I don't blame you for that.
No problem.
It won't end here.
There will be more times when I have to put others in danger, when I'll have to fight or steal to get what I need.
I'm sure I'll pay for it in the end, but I accept that.
It won't stop me.
Because, no matter what, I'll keep going for your sake, and I'm going to get your soul back for you.
Shelra.
How? How could you ever do that?
How could you let Sakura go out there alone?
The compass is broken.
hold on bye you're going out after the princess is that it why do you care if i am don't go
wait for her here with us she might be injured for all we know she's lying out there somewhere
utterly helpless if she doesn't come back i'll never forgive myself for not looking
for not doing something the princess knew how dangerous it was when she decided to go
if she really understood that then why did she go at all
i'm almost there except there's no trail here to follow anymore
who are you she made her choice and i believed her when she promised to come back to those who
were waiting for her so i will wait
well i won't
don't try to stop her or i promise i'll fight you
don't go if you follow her she'll know that you didn't have any faith in her promise
that will wound her more than any physical injury
i know you don't want that so you must let the princess do this on her own
you really are the shower we knew aren't you
sakura
i'm so sorry
you were in such agony i couldn't do anything for you
don't worry about me take care of yourself i'm sure you're in much more pain than i could
even imagine
i'm fine sakura
i'm just so glad
that you're alive after all you've been through
you did well princess consider the price paid in full
i can tell you more about the man who stole your memories
and scattered them across dimensions he's a powerful man named fei wong reed
scattering your feathers and sending you on a journey to find them has been his goal for
for some time why would he want to do that fei wong has a dream when he wants to come
true very badly in order for that to happen he needed two things one of which was the power
of the ruins in cloud country and the other was for you princess to visit many worlds
you would continue to search for your memories you would cross dimensions sometimes even traveling
through time
but when we first left sakura was asleep the whole time everywhere we went
how could she possibly make new memories if she wasn't awake
well there are different types of memories
fei wong isn't interested in ones formed by her heart
he's only concerned with what her body itself can remember
you see your body contains a memory of every world you've visited sakura
you're like a map showing fei wong a path through the dimensions
that's why he turned your memories into feathers and scattered them
so you would follow after them and create that map
fei wong encountered a slight problem however
shaoran knew of this plan so fei wong had to abduct him
in his place he created a clone who would make gathering your feathers his top priority
then he killed karogane's mother and destroyed his country
what does that have to do with it
he made sure you would leave sua and become a warrior
and that you would join princess tomoyo's service and go on a journey
it was my own choice to serve under princess tomoyo
yes the princess believed that as well
which is why she still sent you
even though she was well aware of fei wong's plan
bye the same is true for you
some things were planned and some things were not
but you already know which is which right
princess sakura had to cross many dimensions to create the memories fei wong needed
but she couldn't do it alone
so you were gathered to be her companions
while it's true that you were initially manipulated into beginning this journey
remember that all the choices you have made since then have been yours alone
your thoughts and feelings are under no one else's control
there's no reason for you not to keep making your own decisions
and then i choose to continue my journey
so i can look for shaoran and return his soul to him
remember if you continue traveling through dimensions
you'll do what fei wong planned all along
i know that
but i'm going
well then would it be all right if i join you
you know shaoran's got something of mine
his right eye is my left eye
the magic i still have will call to the magic in that eye
that could be helpful when it comes to tracking him down don't you think
i can't ask you to come unless this is really what you want
you sure that's how you feel five or are you still hiding
this is what i truly want my princess
volcano wants to come too who else
i'm still going to go back to my home world that much is unchanged
i do have a promise to keep after all but i suppose i don't have to go back
right away thank you what about you shaoran
there's something that i need to get back i may not be able to recover it
however i still want to try if that's all right
i understand then the journey will continue this time
because you choose it thanks for treating everyone's wounds we really
appreciate it i'm sorry we couldn't do more
no you've been great thank you and thanks to all the rest of you for your help too
of course i only regret that we couldn't help you more
i'm sorry fuma about your bike and the compass
it's fine don't worry about it but my brother has one of these feathers in his
possession too right i think that's a bigger problem
are you sure we can hold on to this one yes i want it to stay in this world
do you have to leave couldn't you stay for just a little bit longer we'll do all that we can to
heal this world so someday we'll be able to return your feather
i'm sure we'll have it ready by the next time you visit
thanks
who was that girl was she a dream or an illusion
or was she
hey
Hey, I want to know, I want to live. What kind of things do I want to know?
I want to know, I want to know, I want to know, I want to know, I want to know, what kind of things do I want to know?
Thank you.